(Sheldon:)But perhaps
from your lofty heights
(Sheldon:)atop the corporate ladder,
you've lost touch
(Sheldon:)with the struggles
of the common man.
(Leonard:)Look, I'm still happy
to drive you to work.
(Leonard:)Nothing's changed
in that regard.
(Leonard:)We're still roommates,
we're still friends.
(Sheldon:)Except you identified me,
your best friend,
(Sheldon:)as a gangrenous limb
that needed to be severed
(Sheldon:)from the organism
and tossed away.
(Sheldon:)The desperate act
of a little man
(Sheldon:)with a big Napoleon complex.
(Penny:)You know what?
(Leonard:)Go put on your bus pants.
(Raj:)Mm. Last night,
I had a dream
(Raj:)we got so rich from the app,
(Raj:)you and I bought matching
side-by-side mansions.
(Howard:)But...
(Raj:)there was a secret tunnel
(Raj:)connecting your front yard
to my back yard.
(Raj:)What do you think that means?